Guide to the William Tomek papers, 1957-2010
Tomek, William papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
William Tomek papers, 1957-2010
21-43-3918
William G., Tomek 1932-
2 cubic feet.
Publications, Course material
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes publications, presentations and course material.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor emeritus of Applied Economics and Management, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes publications, presentations and course material.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Tomek, William G.,1932-; Cornell University--Faculty.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Economic aspects.; Agricultural prices--United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Publications
  - Publications, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Publications, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Publications, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Publications, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Publications, 1979-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Publications, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Publications, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Publications, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Publications, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Publications, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Publications, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Publications, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Publications, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Publications, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Publications, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Publications, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Publications, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Publications, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Publications, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Publications, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Publications, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Publications, 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Publications, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Masters Thesis - William Tomek, July 1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ph.D. Thesis - William Tomek, August 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Agricultural Product Prices, Tomek and Robinson, 4th Ed. - Data, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Product Prices, Tomek and Robinson - Book Reviews and Publishing Information, 1973; 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Frontiers in Agricultural Marketing Research, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - USDA-NASS Agricultural Prices Panel, June 2009 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Papers on Agricultural Economics - Various Authors (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Series II. Class Materials
  - Econ 101 Notes (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ARME 641, Spring 2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ARME/AEM 641, 1998; 2005; 2007 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - AEM 6410, Spring 2010 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ARME 694, Spring 2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ARME 694 Lectures, Spring 2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ARME 710 - Lecture II, Spring 1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ARME 710, Spring 2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ARME 711, Fall 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Series III. Subject Files
  - University of Nebraska-Lincoln Masters Week, November 3-6, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Agribusiness Economic Outlook Conference, 2004; 2008; 2010 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - W. I. Myers Talk - Ag. History Symposium, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Agricultural Finance and Management Retreat - Syracuse, NY, June 4-5, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American Agricultural Economics Association (AAEA) Newsletters, September 1985-July 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - AAEA Presentation, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Series IV. Biographical
  - Certificate of Appreciation from the Protestant Cooperative Ministry (PCM) at Cornell for Performing Treasurer Duties, June 2007 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - William G. Tomek - Resumes, CVs, Bios (Box 2, Folder 28)